revenueloop.com 2008-06-19

# Revenueloop.com

Privacy **  
** This notice explains RevenueLoop’s online information practices and the choices you can make about the way we collect and use your personal information. You may access our privacy policy from our home page. It is also accessible any time we request your personal information. 

Information We Collect  
This notice applies to all information you submit on the RevenueLoop.com website. On some pages, you can register with RevenueLoop, make requests, and sign up to receive materials. The types of personal information we collect on these pages include: name, address, email address, and phone number.

How We Use Your Information  
All information you provide to Revenue Loop will be used solely for the purpose of furnishing you with the information requested. At no time will we supply your name or any information relating to you to any third parties, other than those you selected to supply you with information. We never use or share your personal information in ways unrelated to those described above, and we prohibit such unrelated uses.

Data Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. To bring our customers and visitors the utmost quality and security, our servers use multiple redundant programs to monitor our site usage 24 hours a day for any unusual activity.

Children's Privacy  
Protecting the privacy of childern is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18 years of age, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18 years old.

How to Contact Us  
Should you have other questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please email us at privacy@RevenueLoop.com.

Disclaimer  
RevenueLoop does not warrant the accuracy or completeness of any information contained on its website and is not responsible for mistakes or omissions. By selecting the enter button to request information, you agree to hold RevenueLoop harmless from any damages incurred as a result of any act or omission by any agent, broker, or service provider to whom you are connected or as a result of your use of any of the information contained on this website. 

*The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on or about November 16, 2006.
